Center Stage: Turn It Up is a drama, music, romance
film directed by Steven Jacobson.
All self-taught dancer Kate Parker has ever wanted to do was
perform with the American Academy of Ballet.
But when she doesnt make it after auditioning, she learns that it takes more
than precision and perfection to succeed in the dance world.
Kate Parker, played by Rachele Brooke Smith.
Tommy Anderson, played by Kenny Wormald.
Suzanne Von Stroh, played by Sarah Jayne Jensen.
Jonathan Reeves, played by Peter Gallagher.
Bella Parker, played by Nicole Muñoz.
Lexi, played by Yan-Kay Crystal Lowe.
Center Stage: Turn It Up is a 2008 dance drama film
and a sequel to Center Stage (2000).
The film was directed by Steven Jacobson and written by Karen Bloch Morse.
The film debuted on Oxygen on November 1, 2008.
It stars Rachele Brooke Smith as Kate Parker and Kenny Wormald as Tommy Anderson, and also features Sarah Jayne Jensen as Suzanne Von Stroh,
with Peter Gallagher and Ethan Stiefel returning from the first film as Jonathan Reeves and Cooper Nielson, respectively.
The film was followed by a sequel Center Stage: On Pointe (2016).
The tone is emotional.